livearealabs.com 2018-05-14

# Privacy Policy | PFSW

Priority Fulfillment Services, Inc. operates the [www.PFSweb.com](http://www.pfsweb.com/), [www.liveareacx.com](http://www.liveareacx.com/) and [www.corporate.PFSweb.com](http://www.corporate.pfsweb.com/) websites, which provide the Service. These websites are owned and operated by Priority Fulfillment Services, Inc. (“PFS”), 505 Millennium Drive, Allen, Texas, 75013.

This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service. Your use of this website will be subject to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this policy, please do not use this website. PFS reserves the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to these terms will be subject to those changes.

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [www.corporate.pfsweb.com](http://www.corporate.pfsweb.com/), unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

**Purpose of processing personal data**

For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes and PFS may collect

  1.     1. Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website including your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, the time and date of your visit, length of visit, page views, the time spent on those pages, and other website navigation statistics and paths
    2. Information that you provide to us when you intentionally registered with our website including your email address
    3. Information that you provide when completing your profile on our website including your name, profile pictures, gender, date of birth, relationship status, interests and hobbies, educational details, and employment details
    4. Information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters including your name and email address
    5. Information that you provide to us when using the Service on our website, or that is generated in the course of the use of those services including the timing, frequency, and pattern of service use
    6. Information relating to any purchases you make of our goods and/or services or any other transactions that you enter into through our website including your name, address, telephone number, email address and card details
    7. Information that you post to our website for publication on the internet including [your user name, your profile pictures and the content of your posts
    8. Information contained in or relating to any communication that you send to us or send through our website including the communication content and metadata associated with the communication
    9. Any other personal information that you choose to send to PFS

**Information Collection and Use**

Personal Information that is collected through forms on our website may be used by us to contact you for marketing purposes. We will ask your explicit consent for direct marketing on the form. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other marketing materials from us as a result of your activity on this website, please inform us via the contact information found on this page. If you register your name, address, e-mail address and/or additional contact information on the website to request marketing materials, we use your information for these purposes. If you object to such use for any reason, you may stop this use either by making an e-mail request, unsubscribing from newsletters, or by sending us a written request.

**Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

PFS will not share your data with third parties.

**_(a) PFS as the Data Controller_**

PFS acts as the Data Controller of any personal data submitted and collected by these websites. Our Data Protection Officer can be contacted at [privacy@pfsweb.com](mailto:privacy@pfsweb.com).

**_(b) International transfers_**

All information submitted to PFS or its subsidiaries will be processed by and may be transferred to and stored using US-based servers managed by PFS or EU-based servers managed by its EU affiliates.

By giving your consent and submitting personal data, you also explicitly agree that your data may be transferred to and processed in the US and/or the EU.

PFS complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from European Union and Switzerland, respectively, to the United States. PFS has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Program, and to view our certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/. ](https://www.privacyshield.gov/.%CA)

**_(c) Appropriate security measures_**

PFS implements appropriate technical and organizational security measures to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction or loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access.

We provide training to our staff on data processing obligations, identification of breaches and risks.

We restrict staff access to personal data to those who need to know.

**_(d) Storage and deletion_**

Your personal data will be processed and maintained in our records as long as your account is active and at the latest 24 months after the last contact, exchange of information or update of data. Please provide us with any relevant modifications and changes in your personal data. Your data will be deleted upon your request.

**Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Type of cookies

  1.     1.       * **Session Cookies** : These are cookies to collect information about what you do during a browsing session each time you visit a Site. When connecting to a server, the device will be allocated a session ID, which enables the server to identify the device during the session and facilitates Site usability. These cookies are temporary and are set to be deleted when leaving a Site or ending a session;
      * **Persistent Cookies** : These are cookies that are stored by your Internet browser for more than a session and are set to expire within a defined time period. Persistent cookies remember and maintain the used settings and information, so one does not have to keep re-entering them whenever visiting a site. They also measure the use and interaction
      * **First-Party Cookies** : These are cookies that are store and accessed on your device. They might include cookies related to third-party service providers. As a result, first-party cookies might log user-related Personal Information accessible to and Processed by third parties.
      * **Third-Party Cookies** : These are cookies that are stored and accessed on your device by third parties determining the purposes and means of the processing of your Personal Information logged by such cookies.

We may engage third-party providers to manage the cookies on our website. These third-party providers may use servers hosted in the US or in the EU. Our website uses these “cookies” to collect information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

**Your rights with regard to the processing of personal data by PFS**

Your rights under this policy and in accordance with the applicable EU GDPR regulations:

  1.     1.       * You have the right of access to personal data; we processed and ask for a copy.
      * You have the right to request a rectification or adaptation of any personal data and information.
      * You have the right to request a restriction of the use of your personal data and information.
      * You have the right to request an erasure of your personal data and information.
      * You have the right to object to processing of your personal data and information
      * You have the right to receive your personal data concerning in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to another controller.
      * You have the right to withdraw consent at any time.

To exercise any of your rights, please send an e-mail to our representative in the EU:

PFSweb  SPRL  
Rue Louis Blériot 5 4460 GRACE-HOLLOGNE, Belgium  
RPM: 466.681.054  
Phone: +32 4 364 41 11  
E-mail: privacy@pfsweb.com

or

Our Head-Office  
Priority Fulfillment Services, Inc.,  
505 Millennium Drive, Allen, Texas, 75013 USA.  
Phone: +1 (972) 881-2900  
E-mail: privacy@pfsweb.com

**Privacy Policy**

In compliance with the EU-US and Swiss-US Privacy Shield Principles, PFS commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union or Swiss individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact the PFS Data Protection Officer at: [privacy@PFSweb.com](mailto:webmaster@PFSweb.com).

PFS has further committed to refer any unresolved privacy complaints under the Privacy Shield Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit http://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers for more information or to issue a complaint.

A complaint with regard to the handling of personal data and the applicable GDPR regulations can also be made with the supervisory authority of our representative in Belgium.

Commission for the Protection of Privacy  
Rue de la Presse 35, 1000 Brussels  
+32 (0)2 274 48 00  
commission@privacycommission.be

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. Changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at:

Our Headquarters  
Priority Fulfillment Services, Inc.,  
505 Millennium Drive, Allen, Texas, 75013 USA.  
Phone: +1 (972) 881-2900  
E-mail: [privacy@pfsweb.com](mailto:privacy@pfsweb.com)

or our EU offices

PFSweb  SPRL  
Rue Louis Blériot 5 4460 GRACE-HOLLOGNE, Belgium  
RPM: 466.681.054  
Phone: +32 4 364 41 11  
E-mail: privacy@pfsweb.com
